BRAC Additional Records 5735
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Strikes, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  January 1, 1967-December 31, 1967
- Strikes, 1969-1975 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  October 1969-1975
- Strikes - 1965 Canadian Wage Movement, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Strikes - National 1966 Wage and Rules Movement - Certification of Strike Ballots by Region (Western) (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Strikes - Circular of April 13, 1970; Ballots; Final Tabulation on Strike Ballot (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Railroad Strike Insurance, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  September 1978
- Target - GE!: A report of the national support project and consumer boycott sponsored by National American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) in the 100-day GE strike that started October 26, 1969. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Strikes - 1966 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 38, Folder 6)
  See Separate File for Certification of Strike Ballots
- Strikes: Airline Strike Against Five Carriers, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Strikes - National 1966 Wage and Rules Movement - Certification of Strike Ballots by Region (Eastern) (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Strikes - 1966 National Wage and Rules Movement - Certification of Strike Ballots by Region (Southeastern) (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Strikes: Community Cabs, Incorporated. Jacksonville, Florida, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Strike - Clerks, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Strikes - 1969 Movements, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  January-November 1970
- Strikes - 1969 Movements, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  November 1-30, 1970
- Strikes - 1969 Movement, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  December 1-15, 1970
- Strikes - 1969 Movement, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  December 1970-January 31, 1971
- Strikes - 1969 Movements, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  February 1, 1971-August 13, 1971
- Strikes (General), 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1971-January 14, 1972
- Strikes - 1974 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Strikes - 1972 Wage and Rules Movement (Canada), 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Seaboard Coast Line, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Seawell Authority Aqueductos, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Strikes - Belt Railway of Chicago, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Strikes - Ogilvie Flour Mills Company, Limited, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Strike - Chicago and North Western, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Strike - Chicago and North Western, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Strike - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad (Case Number 67 c 731), 1967 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Strikes - Rio Grande Employees Hospital Association, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Strikes - Erie-Lackawanna Railroad, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Grand Trunk Western, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Strikes - Grand Trunk Railroad Company (Patrolmen), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Strikes - Houston Belt and Terminal, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  Notice December 16, 1965
- Strikes - Illinois Central, 1962-1964 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  Piggyback notice dated May 16, 1962. Rules Revision notice dated October 12, 1964.
- Strikes - Kansas City Terminal, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  Notices: April 11, 1962; August 8, 1962; July 25, 1963; July 26, 1963
- Strikes - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  Carriers Notices: July 7, 1964; July 30, 1964; August 13, 1964. Organization Notices: July 24, 1964; August 8, 1964.
- Strikes - Dorcar, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Lehigh Valley Railroad Company, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Strikes - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Missouri Pacific Railroad (Gulf District), 1964 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  Carrier unilaterally placed into effect the hiring and the using of persons not covered by the scope of the Clerks' Agreement for the purpose of unloading trucks of the Tennessee Pacific-Missouri Pacific Freight Warehouse at New Orleans, Louisiana.
- Strikes - Northwestern Pacific Railroad, 1958-1963 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  Stabilization of employment notice September 22, 1958.
- Strikes - Northwestern Pacific, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  Notice June 3, 1963 Wage Demand.
- C.L. Dennis: Saint Augustine Conference to Formulate Brotherhood of Railway Clerks Program on Florida East Coast Railway, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Strikes - Distribution and Transportation Services, Incorporated, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Strikes - WFA Trucking Company, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  WFA?
- Strikes - Penn Central, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Strikes - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  February-September 17, 1979. Includes Bound Materials.
- Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  September 18, 1979-October 9, 1979
- Chicago, Rock Island, and Pacific Railroad Company, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  October 10, 1979
- Rock Island Strike - Newspaper Articles, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  August 28-October 5, 1979
- Railway Clerk Interchange- Strike Releases, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  August 28-October 4, 1979
- Rock Island Strike - Telegrams, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Rock Island Strike - J.J. Witmeyer, Junior, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Rock Island Strike - Legal Papers, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  March 1976
- Strikes - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines), 1965-1966 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  Notice of October 12, 1965 Rules. Notice of October 27, 1965 Rules. Carriers' Notice of January 21, 1966 to Cancel All Agreements and Substitute Attachment "A" Therefore.
- Strikes - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines): Work Stoppage on or About September 8 at Sacramento and Roseville California, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Strikes - Southern Pacific, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  Notice dated January 24, 1964 served on Southern Pacific to provide protection for employees adversely affected by Carrier's proposed transfers (i.e. TOPS Consolidation of Division, etcetera) under existing and contemplated notices
- Strikes - Southern Pacific (Pacific Lines), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  Southern Pacific versus Brotherhood of Railway Clerks; System Board, Weaver, LaFranchi et al
- Strikes - Southern Pacific, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Strikes - Southern Rail, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Strikes - Texas and Pacific, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  Notice of August 2, 1966 regarding jury duty and sick leave pay
- Strikes - Interstate Railroad, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Strikes - Union Pacific, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Whether Strike Benefits are Subject to Income Tax, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; Strike to be called for 6:00am Eastern Time Wednesday January 23, 1963
- Strikes - Florida East Coast, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  January 1972
- Strikes - Florida East Coast (Special Account), 1965 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Special Fund to be Equally Administered by R.M. Mayberry at Saint Augustine and Don K. Campbell at Miami, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Assessments, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; strike called 6:00am Eastern Time, Wednesday January 23, 1963
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Trans-Communication Employees Union, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Strikes- Florida East Coast, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; Strike to be called for 6:00 am Eastern Standard Time, Wednesday January 23, 1963. "Phase Out"
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Appeal: Mrs. Betty Jeanne Dean, 1965 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - "Defense Fund", 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Applications for Membership, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  Regarding Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; Strike to be called for 6:00am Eastern Standard Time Wednesday, January 23, 1963. November 1964.
- Barrons Newspaper: "The Florida East Coast Railway Strike May Cost Labor Dear", 1965 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  April 12, 1965
- Florida East Coast Railway Company - Annual Report, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Special File: Letters to Congressmen Regarding Resolution, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  February 26, 1965. Regarding Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; Strike to be called for 6:00am Eastern Standard Time, Wednesday, January 23, 1963.
- Strikes - Florida East Coast - Special File: Brotherhood of Railway Clerks Establishment of Own Facilities, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Regarding Joint 1961 Wage and Rules Movement; Strike to be called for 6:00am Eastern Standard Time, Wednesday, January 23, 1963.
- Rules - Florida East Coast - Mediation Case, 1963-1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  Mediation Case: Desire of the Florida East Coast Railway to supersede the seventeen separate collective bargaining agreements. Carrier's Formal Notice served September 24, 1963. Also October 14, 1965. Includes Bound Materials.
- Strikes - Elgin, Joliet, and Eastern Railway, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  Unauthorized Strike took place May 3, 1967.
- Strikes - Louis Dreyfus, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  March 18, 1964 Notice. June 4, 1971 Notice.
- Strikes - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway (Chesapeake District), 1974 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Strikes - Universal Carloading and Distributing Company, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  Notice July 12, 1966. Strike Ballot August 7, 1969.
- Strikes - Freight Forwarding, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Strikes - Chicago Union Station, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  On August 26, 1966 our members of Chicago Union Station engaged in a short strike - this strike was not formally authorized.
- Strikes - Affco Packing Company, Incorporated, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Koppers Company, Incorporated, Forest Products Division, Galesburg, Illinois, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  September 1973
- Strikes - Koppers Company, Incorporated, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  Notice September 28, 1964.
- Strikes - Long Island Rail Road Company, 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  Employees' Section 6 Notice of October 1, 1971 Covering Wages and Rules
- Strikes - Long Island, 1967-1970 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  Wage Notices November 20, 1967 (E-333) and 1970 (E-355)
- Strikes - Long Island, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Strikes - Long Island (Newspaper Information), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  December 1972
- Strikes - Canadian Steamship Lines, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Cincinnati Union Terminal, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Strikes - Panda Terminals, Incorporated, 1967-1969 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  Strike Ballot August 7, 1969.
- Strikes - Harbor Belt Line, 1964-1966 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  Notice December 11, 1964.
- Strikes - Acme Fast Freight, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  Notice of February 28, 1963
- Strikes - National Carloading Corporation, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Strikes - Acme Fast Freight, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  Notice of July 12, 1966 and Strike Ballot of August 7, 1969.
- Strikes - Fort Smith Bus Depot (Operated as a joint enterprise by Crown Coach Company and Oklahoma Transportation Company), 1966-1967 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  Notice served December 29, 1966.
- Strikes - Pacific Car Demurrage Bureau, 1958-1963 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  Stabilization of Employment notice September 22, 1958.
- Strikes - Pacific Car Demurrage Bureau, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Strikes - ABC Freight Forwarding Company, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  Notice: July 12, 1966. Strike Ballot: August 7, 1969.
- Board of Adjustment - Akron, Canton and Youngstown and Transportation Communication Employees Union, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 32)
- Strikes - Republic Carloading Company, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 33)
- Strikes - International Forwarding Company, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 34)
- Strikes - Lifschultz Fast Freight, 1966-1969 (Box 41, Folder 35)
- Strikes - Delaware and Hudson, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  March 1974
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  July 10-August 25, 1978
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western Railway Company - Strike Fund, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  July 25, 1978-September 25, 1978
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  September 26, 1978-October 15, 1978
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  October 16, 1978-October 31, 1978
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  November 1, 1978-December 31, 1978
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Norfolk and Western - Illegal Strikes, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Strikes - Highway and City Transportation, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Strike Ballot August 7, 1969
- Strikes - Duluth, Minnesota and Iron Range Railway, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Strikes - Detroit, Toledo, and Ironton, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Strikes - Eastern Greyhound Lines, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  Notice December 29, 1964.
- Strikes - Saint Joseph Terminal, 1964-1965 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  Notice: November 4, 1964.
- Strikes - Trailways Bus Depot Chicago, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Strikes - East Portland Freight Terminal, 1958-1963 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  Stabilization of Employment Notice: September 22, 1958
- Strikes - East Portland Freight, 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  Wage Demand Notice: June 3, 1963.
- Strikes - Fruit Growers Express, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Strikes - Airline Foods, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Wages - Toledo, Peoria, and Western Railroad, 1950 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Strikes - Caribbean Atlantic Airlines, Incorporated, 1966-1967 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  Notice: November 4, 1966.
- Strikes - Caribbean Atlantic Airlines, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Strikes - Memphis Leasing Company, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Mississippi Central, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Strikes - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1958-1963 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  Stabilization of Employment Notice September 22, 1958.
- Strikes - Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Strikes - Southwestern Freight Bureau, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Strikes - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  July 19, 1973
- Strikes - Midwest Bus Lines, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  Trailways Bus Defeat, Little Rock, Arkansas. Notice Dated March 1, 1966.
- Strikes - Northwest Airlines, Incorporated - C.L. Dennis' Personal Working Papers (Box 42, Folder 28)
- Strikes - Northwest Airlines, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  Notice dated June 28, 1966. Rules and Wages.
- Strikes - Northwest Airlines, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 30)
- Strikes - Northwest Airlines, 1970-1982 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  December 1. 1970-June 17, 1982
- Strikes - Northwest Airlines, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Strikes - Pullman Company - Pennsylvania taking over Pullman cars, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Strikes - Salt Lake Stock Yards Operation Company, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Pacific Great Eastern, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Name Changed to British Columbia Railroad in 1972
- Strikes - Allied Maintenance Corp, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Western Airlines, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Providence and Worcester Railroad Company (General), 1982 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  May 1982
- Peoria Terminal Company (General), 1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Strikes - Braniff Airways, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Strikes - Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  Concerning our dispute with the Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific in the joint movement to persuade Carrier to retain the group life insurance policy which has been in effect for some time and, at the same time, adopt and apply the terms of the august 19, 1960
- Strikes - Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  July 15, 1967
- Strikes - Trans-Continental Freight Bureau, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  Notice dated February 4, 1964. Auto Allowance.
- Strikes - Transportation Hospital Association, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Strikes - REA Express, Incorporated versus Brotherhood of Railway and Airline Clerks et al. - United States District Court, District 8, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  Strike Called April 19, 1971. Court Case May 13, 1971.
- Strikes - REA Express, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Strikes - REA Express - Work Stoppage at Birmingham, Alabama, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Strikes - REA Express - 1965 Wage Movement, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Strikes - REA Express - Work Stoppage at Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Strikes - REA Express, Incorporated, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Strikes - REA Express - Work Stoppage at Atlanta, Georgia, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Strikes - REA Express - Work Stoppage at Dallas, Texas, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Strikes - REA Express - Wildcat Strike, Chicago Illinois, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Strikes - REA Express - Lodge 2005 Baltimore, Maryland, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Strikes - REA Express - Lodge 2029 (Unauthorized), 1967 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Strikes - REA Express - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  March 1967
- Strikes - REA Express, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Strikes - REA Express, Incorporated, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Strikes - REA Express - Work Stoppage at REA in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 29)
  February 6, 1967
- Strikes - River Terminal, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  Section 6 notice of August 21, 1967
- Strikes - Chicago Heights Terminal Transfer, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Strikes - Algona Central Railway, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Strikes - Southern California Rapid Transit District, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 33)
  Notice: March 28, 1966
- Strikes - REA Express, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Strikes - CP Express, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Strikes - SP Brooklyn Federal Credit Union, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Strikes - Saint Petersburg and North Pinellas Limousine Service Incorporated, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Strikes - Yellow Cabs of Miami, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Strikes - Yellow and Diamond Cab Companies, Tampa, Florida, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 39)
- Strikes - Associated Diamond Cabs, Incorporated, Miami, Florida, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 40)
- Strikes - Pacific Fruit Express, 1963-1964 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  Wage Demand Notice: June 3, 1963
- Strikes - Pacific Fruit Express, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 42)
  Notice: May 6, 1963.
- Strikes - Pacific Fruit Express, 1963 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  Notice: March 5, 1963
- Strikes - Pacific Fruit Express, 1958-1963 (Box 43, Folder 44)
- Strikes - Hollywood Accessories, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 45)
- Strikes - National Cash Register, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 46)
- Strikes - National Cash Register Company, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 47)
- Strikes - National Cash Register, Johnstown, Pennsylvania, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Strikes - National Cash Register, New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1945-1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  1945-September 1973
- National Association of General Chairmen - Eastern Region, 1974-1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  January 1, 1974-October 1979
- Regional Association of General Chairmen - Western, 1969-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  January 3, 1969-July 1978
- Regional Association of General Chairmen, 1958-1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  1958-September 1975
- Regional Association of General Chairmen - Airline Boards of Adjustment, 1957-1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  1957-June 1979
- By-Laws - Eastern Regional Association, 1932-1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  1932-Setpemebr 1974
- By-Laws - Western Regional Association, 1923-1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  1923-July 1975
- By-Laws - Regional Association (Airline), 1957-1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  1957-November 1974
- Ritual (General), 1930-1971 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  1930-July 1971
- Financial Assistance - Boards of Adjustment, 1960-1973 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  1960-May 1973
- Life Membership (General), 1924-1974 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  1924-March 1974
- National Mediation Board - Mediator's Manual, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Wages - Shop Crafts Movement (Emergency Board Reports, 1968-1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- National Mediation Board (General), 1971-1977 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  1971-December 1977
- National Mediation Board (General), 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  January 1978-1979
- National Mediation Board - craft or Class Hearings (Airlines), 1970-1979 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- National Mediation Board - Mediators, 1935-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  1935-October 1977
- National Mediation Board - Annual Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  1972-April 1976
- National Mediation Board - Unsettled Submissions, 1966-1971 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  January 1, 1966-October 1971
- National Mediation Board - Unsettled Submissions and International President's Bulletins, 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  August 1964-February 1970
- National Mediation Board - "C" Cases; Certifications Withdrawn or Dismissed, 1965-1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  1965-November 1974
- National Mediation Board - Emergency Board Reports (Since Railway Labor Act was Amended in 1934), 1955-1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  August 1955-1979. Includes Bound Materials
- National Mediation Board - Interpretations, 1961-1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  Missing: 1-87; 89-94; 96; 98-99; 103-104; 109; 111-116.
- Reciprocal Membership Transfer (General), 1930-1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  1930-May 1973
- Reciprocal Membership Transfer - Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1922-1927 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Reciprocal Membership Transfer - International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Reciprocal Membership Transfer - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, 1931 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- 1977 Rules and Wage Movements - Des Moines Union Railway (Box 45, Folder 12)
- State Legislative Committee (General), 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  July 1977-December 6, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - California, Region IV, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  July 1977-August 14, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Colorado, Region IV, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  July 1977-March 14, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Georgia, Region I, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  July-September 2, 1977
- State Legislative Committee - Illinois, Region II, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  July 1977-February 12, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Indiana, Region II, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  July 1977-September 6, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Kansas, Region III, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  July 1977-August 9, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Massachusetts, Region I, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  July 1977-January 12, 1979
- State Legislative Committee - Minnesota, Region II, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  July 1977-August 16, 1978
- Group Insurance (General), 1952-1979 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  1952-October 1979
- Parcel Post (General), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Dominion of Canada (General), 1964-1977 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  January 1, 1964-October 1977. Includes Bound Materials.
- Dominion of Canada - Unemployment Insurance, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  August 1, 1970. Includes Bound Materials
- Submission to the Government of Canada, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  Bound. March 6, 1973
- Canadian Railway Labour Association to the Hall Commission on Pensions, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Dominion of Canada - Associated Railway Organizations, 1960-1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  1960-January 1976
- Dominion of Canada - Canadian Labor Relations Board, 1954-1976 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  1954-February 1976
- Dominion of Canada - Research Bureau - Cooperating Railway Labor Unions, 1959-1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  1959-January 1973
- United States Mail (General), 1969-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  January 1, 1969-1974
- Abandonments - Baltimore and Ohio: Abandonment of Operation between Toledo, Ohio and Detroit, Michigan, 1962-1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  1962-May 1972